Thomas Foxen Anderson Papers 1928-1989 Mss.Ms.Coll.75
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1932-1989; 15 boxes; 7.5 linear feet
  - Columbia University Press, 1949-1950 (Box 3)
  - Comer, Joseph J., 1957, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils, 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Conference on Respiratory Disease, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Conference on the Control of Form in Cells, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    Porter, Keith R.
    Satir, Peter
    Simon, Lee D.
  - Conference on Transfer RNA, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Congrès International de Microscopie Électronique, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Convey, John H., 1955 (Box 4)
  - Corbett, M.K., 1962 (Box 4)
  - Cornell University, 1960-1967 (Box 4)
  - Coryell, Charles, 1942 (Box 4)
  - Cosslett, V.E., 1961 (Box 4)
    -See also Ser.I, International Conference on Electron Microscopy
  - Cowles, John (Jack), 1958 (Box 4)
  - Crawford, Bryce L., Jr., 1938 (Box 4)
  - Crawford, Irving, 1978 (Box 4)
  - Crick, Francis, 1954, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Crow, James F., 1968, 1975-1976; 6.0 Item(s) (Box 4)
    -See also Ser.I, Genetics
    Bacterial genetics; Human genetics; Molecular genetics; Population genetics; Publication; Referee's report; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
  - Cummings, Donald S., 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Curtiss, Roy III, 1978 (Box 4)
  - Dalton, Albert J., 1955, 1970-1972 (Box 4)
  - Daniels, Farrington, 1940-1955 (Box 4)
  - Danon, David, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Danovich, John F., 1961 (Box 4)
  - Darlington, J.M. (Jim), 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Das Gupta, N.N., 1965-1966 (Box 4)
  - Davies, R.E. (Bob), 1962, 1965 (Box 4)
  - Davis, Bernard D., 1965 (Box 4)
  - Davis, Herbert L., 1953 (Box 4)
    Chance, Britton
  - Davis, Marguerite, 1953 (Box 4)
  - Davison, Peter F., 1963 (Box 4)
  - Dawes, Geoffrey, 1949 (Box 4)
  - de Duve, Christian, 1978 (Box 4)
  - de Ruyck, R., 1953 (Box 4)
  - de Souza Santos, Persio, 1955 (Box 4)
    de Souza Santos, Helena
  - De Taxis du Poët, Philippe, 1985 (Box 4)
  - DeCew, Walter M., 1964-1965 (Box 4)
  - DeLamater, Edward D., 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Delbrück, Max, 1942-1969, n.d.; 38.0 Item(s) (Box 4)
    -See also Ser.I, Association of Philadelphia Scientists
    Bacterial genetics; Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Delbruck, Max. 60th birthday; Honors -- Horwitz Prize; Honors -- National Medal of Science; Invitations; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Luria, Salvador Edward; Molecular genetics; Poetry and literature; Publication; Radiation genetics; Recommendations; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Demerec, Milislav, 1942-1966; 7.0 Item(s) (Box 4)
    -See also Ser.I, John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Cancer, chemotherapy; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Marine Biological Laboratory, Woods Hole; Mirsky, Alfred Ezra; Molecular genetics
  - Denues, A.R.T., 1953-1961, n.d. (Box 4)
    Wyckoff, Ralph W.G.
  - Deonier, Richard, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Desikachary, T.V., 1954 (Box 4)
  - D'Eustachio, Anthony, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Deutch, Bernhard, 1948-1954 (Box 4)
  - DeVault, Don, 1937 (Box 4)
    Yost, Don M.
  - Dickerson, Roy E., 1944 (Box 4)
  - Dmochowski, Leon, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Doermann, A.H. (Gus), 1950-1952, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Donoso, Larry A., 1987 (Box 4)
  - Dorsey, John R., 1960 (Box 4)
  - Duggar, B.M., 1941 (Box 4)
  - Dulbecco, Renato, 1950, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
    -See also Ser.I, The Salk Institute for Biological Studies
  - Dupouy, G., 1959-1970 (Box 4)
  - Dürwald, Hildegard, 1961, 1963 (Box 4)
  - du Vigneaud, Vincent, 1945 (Box 4)
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Edgar, Robert S., 1966-1967 (Box 4)
    Eiserling, Fred A.
  - Eisenstark, Abe, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Eiserling, Fred A., 1967 (Box 4)
    -See also Ser.I, Edgar, Robert S.
  - Elbertson, Barbara J., 1978 (Box 4)
  - Electron Microscope Society of America, 1952-1978 (Box 4)
    Breese, Sidney S., Jr.
    Preuss, Luther E.
  - Elford, W.J., 1950 (Box 4)
  - Ellis, Emory L., 1943 (Box 4)
  - English, Sally Park, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Engstrom, Arne, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Espejo, Romilio T., 1971 (Box 4)
  - Eubanks, Kathie Lynn, 1984 (Box 4)
  - European Regional Conference on Electron Microscopy, 1956, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Evans, Susan C., 1964 (Box 4)
  - Everhart, T.E., 1959 (Box 4)
  - Eyring, Henry, 1941-1942, 1954 (Box 4)
  - Fajans, Kasimir, 1932, 1940, 1956 (Box 4)
    some in German
  - Falkow, S., 1978 (Box 4)
  - The Faraday Society, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Farrant, John, 1958 (Box 4)
  - Fawcett, Don W., 1959 (Box 5)
  - Feinstein, Robert N., 1959 (Box 5)
  - Feldman, William, 1955 (Box 5)
  - Fenner, Frank, 1977-1987 (Box 5)
  - Fernandez-Moran, Humberto, 1957-1968 (Box 5)
    Robinson, John
  - Fernholm, Bo, 1979 (Box 5)
    -See also Ser.I, Simon, Lee D.
  - Finegold, Leonard, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Fisher, Agnes, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Fisher, Harold W., 1977 (Box 5)
  - Fisher, Ken W., 1958 (Box 5)
  - Fleischer, Sidney, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Flexner, Louis B., 1954, 1958 (Box 5)
  - Forro, Frederick, Jr., 1960 (Box 5)
  - Fowler, Catherine B. (Box 5)
    -See Ser.I, Rappaport, Catherine Fowler
  - Fowler, R.H., n.d. (Box 5)
  - Fox, Sidney W., 1946, 1955 (Box 5)
  - Frankel, Fred R., 1969-1976 (Box 5)
  - Franklin, Naomi, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
    -See also Ser.I, Brownstein, Barbara, 1962
  - Franklin, Richard, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Frazer, John E., 1942 (Box 5)
  - Fred, E.B., 1941, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Frederickson, Donald S., 1978 (Box 5)
  - Freed, Jerome J., 1973 (Box 5)
  - Friedenberg, Robert, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Friedman, Murray, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Fuerst, Clarence R., 1957-1958 (Box 5)
  - Ernest F. Fullham, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Funk, Fred D., 1967 (Box 5)
  - Fussell, Catharine, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Gak, Ernst F., [1949] (Box 5)
    Pirie, N.W.
  - Gall, Joseph G., 1976, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Galtsoff, Paul S., 1942 (Box 5)
  - Garen, Alan, 1957-1963, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Garen, Suzanne, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Garfinkel, Lillian, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Gay, Helen, 1952-1964, n.d. (Box 5)
  - General Electric Company, 1942 (Box 5)
  - Genetics, 1968-1976; 15.0 Item(s) (Box 5)
    Crow, James F.
    Caspari, Ernst W.
    Bacterial genetics; Biographical and personal data -- Schultz, Jack; Caspari, Ernst Wilhelm; Crow, James F.; Drosophila genetics; Molecular genetics; National Academy of Sciences; Publication -- Genetics; Referee's report; Schultz, Jack
  - Genetics Society of America. Committee on Historical Documents, 1978; 3.0 Item(s) (Box 5)
    American Philosophical Society; Committee activities; Genetics Society of America; History of biology, especially genetics; Preservation of historical materials; Sonneborn, Tracy M.
  - Gerhardt, Philipp, 1965 (Box 5)
    -See also Ser.I, American Society for Microbiology
  - Germer, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Gewanter, Robert, 1955 (Box 5)
  - Gibbons, Ian Read, 1956-1964 (Box 5)
    -See also Ser.I, American Society for Cell Biology
  - Gibson, Dean W., 1968 (Box 5)
  - Gille, Alain, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Ginsberg, Harold S., 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Glaser, Donald A., 1967 (Box 5)
  - Glaser, Elizabeth B., 1942 (Box 5)
  - Glaser, O.C., 1942 (Box 5)
  - Glass, Bentley (Box 5)
    -See Ser.I, Science
  - Glauert, Audrey M., 1961 (Box 5)
  - Gledhill, Barton L., 1972 (Box 5)
  - Glusker, Donald, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Goldberg, Herbert S., 1961 (Box 5)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company, 1942 (Box 5)
  - Gordan Research Conferences, 1960-1961, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Gordan, Francis B., 1950 (Box 5)
  - Graham, Angus F., 1958-1974 (Box 5)
    Millward, Stewart
    Reichman, M.E.
  - Granboulan, Philippe, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Gray, Irving, 1972 (Box 5)
  - Green, David E., 1947-1949, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Green, Robert H., 1942 (Box 5)
  - Greenberg, Jay, 1972 (Box 5)
  - Greenspan, Neil Sanford, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Grube, William L., 1956 (Box 5)
  - Guha, Arabindo, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Gunsalus, I.C., 1956-1966 (Box 5)
  - Guttman, Burton S., 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Hagen, George L., 1973 (Box 5)
  - Hagopian, Arpi, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Haguenau, Françoise, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Hall, Cecil E., 1945-1964, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Halpern, B. David, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Halpern, Jules, 1956 (Box 6)
  - Halverson, Valerie S., 1966 (Box 6)
  - Hanawalt, Philip Courtland, 1959-1961 (Box 6)
  - Hane, Michael W., 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Hansburg, Daniel, n.d. (Box 6)
  - Hardco International, Inc., 1958 (Box 6)
  - Harding, Clifford V., 1961 (Box 6)
  - Harker, David, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Harper and Row, Publishers, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Hart, Hiram, 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Hartman, Philip E., 1955-1965 (Box 6)
    -See also Ser.I, Walker, Donald H., Jr.
  - Harvey, Ethel Browne, 1943 (Box 6)
  - Haskins Laboratories, 1941 (Box 6)
  - Hastings, E.G., 1940 (Box 6)
  - Hauschka, Theodore, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Hawley, R. Scott, 1981-1982 (Box 6)
  - Hayes, William, 1957-1958, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Hazel, Fred, 1963 (Box 6)
  - Heidelberger, Michael, 1941-1942 (Box 6)
  - Heinmets, Ferdinand, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Henkel, Joel, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Henle, Gertrude, 1979 (Box 6)
  - Henle, Werner, 1953-1965 (Box 6)
  - Hepfer, Carol, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Hercules Powder Company, 1943-1944 (Box 6)
  - Herman, Robert K., 1960 (Box 6)
  - Hermann Editions Scientifiques, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Herriott, Roger M., 1951, 1966, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Herrmann, F.J., 1962 (Box 6)
  - Hershey, Alfred D., 1950, 1953, 1961; 7.0 Item(s) (Box 6)
    Bacterial genetics; Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Invitations; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Herskowitz, [Irwin H.], n.d. (Box 6)
  - Heston, Walt E., 1963 (Box 6)
  - Hewitt, A. Tyl, 1977, n.d. (Box 6)
  - Heyn, A.N.J., 1965 (Box 6)
  - Higgins, Michael L., 1967 (Box 6)
  - Hilbig, A., 1960 (Box 6)
  - Hillier, James, 1942-1943 (Box 6)
  - Hirano, Tadashi, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Hoffman, Charles W., 1944 (Box 6)
  - Hoffman, Joseph F., 1955 (Box 6)
  - Hoffmann-Berling, Hartmut, 1963 (Box 6)
  - Hofschneider, Peter H., 1971 (Box 6)
  - Hogman, David, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Holbert, Pauline E., 1961 (Box 6)
  - Holmes, Francis O., 1940 (Box 6)
  - Holmes, Ian Hamilton, 1962-1970 (Box 6)
  - Holt, Stanley C., 1975 (Box 6)
  - Hoppe, Walter, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Hosoda, Junko, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Hotchkiss, Rollin D., 1977-1978 (Box 6)
    Schaeffer, Pierre
  - Hotz, G., 1953 (Box 6)
  - "How About...", 1980 (Box 6)
  - Howard, Jack B., 1938 (Box 6)
  - Hufnagel, Linda Ann, 1966-1968 (Box 6)
  - Hughes, Inge M., 1952 (Box 6)
  - Hummeler, Klaus, 1961, 1963 (Box 6)
  - Hungerford, David A., 1973 (Box 6)
  - Huppert, Charles H., 1959 (Box 6)
  - Hurwitz, Jerard, 1961, 1972 (Box 6)
  - Hurwitz, Sue, 1955, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Hutchinson, Franklin, 1966-1982 (Box 6)
  - Hutchinson, W.G., 1959, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Inglis, Sarah Park (Sally), 1960-1961, 1976 (Box 6)
  - The Institute for Cancer Research, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Folder #1, 1960-1980 (Box 6)
    - Folder #2, 1981-1983, n.d. (Box 6)
  - Institute for Medical Research, 1967-1971 (Box 6)
  - Institute for Scientific Information, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Instituto Nacional de Enfermedádes Neoplásicas, 1961 (Box 6)
  - Instrument Society of America, 1955 (Box 6)
  - International Committee on Nomenclature of Viruses, 1966-1971 (Box 6)
    Bradley, David E.
    Fenner, Frank
    Kaiser, Dale
    Wildy, Peter
  - International Conference on Electron Microscopy, 1953-1954, 1957, 1962 (Box 7)
  - International Congress for Microbiology, 1953, 1958 (Box 7)
  - International Congress of Physiological Sciences, 1967 (Box 7)
    Pappenheimer, John R.
  - International Congress on Photobiology, 1953 (Box 7)
    Latarjet, Raymond
  - International Federation of Societies for Electron Microscopy, 1964-1967, 1987 (Box 7)
    Poole, Jan B.
  - International Organization for Pure and Applied Biophysics, 1964, 1966 (Box 7)
  - International Society for Cell Biology, 1960-1962 (Box 7)
  - International Union for Pure and Applied Biophysics, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Folder #1, 1966-Apr. 1970 (Box 7)
    - Folder #2, Jun. 1970-1973 (Box 7)
  - Interscience Publishers, Inc., 1941 (Box 7)
  - Intervirology, 1972-1977 (Box 7)
  - Israel, Vance, 1965-1971, n.d. (Box 7)
    -See also Ser.I, Levine, Myron
  - Itokawa, Hideo, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Jackson, Richard W., [1945] (Box 7)
  - Jacob, François, 1957-1978, n.d. (Box 7)
    -See also Ser.I, Colloque de Royaumont
    -See also Ser.I, Wollman, Elie
  - Jacobson, A.P., 1982 (Box 7)
  - Jacobson, Leon O., 1965 (Box 7)
  - Jahn, E.C., 1942 (Box 7)
  - Jakob, A., 1950 (Box 7)
  - Jean, Marcel, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Jeanes Hospital, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Jerne, Niels K., 1961-1962 (Box 7)
  - Jesaitis, 1961 (Box 7)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1959, 1961 (Box 5)
    Demerec, M.
  - Johnson, Frank H., 1941 (Box 7)
  - Jones, Grinnell, 1940 (Box 7)
  - Journal de Microscopie, 1965-1971 (Box 7)
  - Journal of Applied Physics, 1942-1957 (Box 7)
  - Journal of Bacteriology, 1951-1972 (Box 7)
    -See also Ser.I, Luria, Salvador E., 10 Feb. 1972
  - Journal of Electronmicroscopy, 1960 (Box 7)
  - Journal of Molecular Biology, 1965-1973 (Box 7)
  - Journal of the American Chemical Society, 1943 (Box 7)
  - Journal of Ultrastructure Research, 1968, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Journal of Virology, 1966-1975 (Box 7)
    Kozloff, Lloyd M.
  - Jungeblut, Claus W., 1942 (Box 7)
  - Kabrich, W.C., 1941 (Box 7)
  - Kahn, Barbara, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Kaiser, Dale, 1961, 1982, n.d. (Box 7)
    -See also Ser.I, Journal of Molecular Biology
  - Kalckar, Herman M., 1952 (Box 7)
  - Kaudewitz, F., 1958 (Box 7)
  - Kauffman, George B., 1983-1984 (Box 7)
  - Kaufmann, Berwind P., 1961 (Box 7)
  - Kawabe, Osamu, 1962 (Box 7)
  - Kay, Lily E., 1986 (Box 7)
  - Kehler, H., 1960 (Box 7)
  - Keiper, David Allen, 1958-1959 (Box 7)
  - Kelemen, Mary V., 1957 (Box 7)
  - Kellenberger, Eduard, 1953-1978, n.d. (Box 7)
    -See also Ser.I, Gordon Research Conferences
  - Keller, A., 1959 (Box 7)
  - Kelly, Thomas A., 1968 (Box 7)
  - The Jackson Laboratory, 1977 (Box 7)
  - The Johns Hopkins University, 1941-1965 (Box 7)
  - The Journal of Cell Biology, 1965 (Box 7)
  - The Journal of Chemical Physics, 1936, 1938 (Box 7)
  - The Journal of Experimental Medicine, 1942-1943 (Box 7)
  - The Journal of General Physiology, 1951-1952 (Box 7)
  - Kempner, Ellis Stanley, 1952-1953, 1960 (Box 8)
    Biophysical Journal
  - Kempton, J.H., 1941 (Box 8)
  - The Joseph P. Kennedy, Jr. Foundation, 1971 (Box 8)
  - Kennedy, Simon C., 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Kilkson, Rein, 1962 (Box 8)
  - Kim, Sun Kee (Box 8)
    -See Ser.I, Walker, Donald H., Jr.
  - Kim, Sung-How, 1974 (Box 8)
  - King, E.S., 1943 (Box 8)
  - King, Thomas J., 1971-1973 (Box 8)
  - Kinsbourne, Marcel, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Kirkpatrick, Paul H., 1959 (Box 8)
  - Klein, Richard, 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Kleinschmidt, A.K., 1964-1965 (Box 8)
  - Klimenko, Sergei, 1963, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Klug, Aaron, 1965 (Box 8)
  - Kluyver, A.J., 1950 (Box 8)
  - Knaysi, Georges, 1967 (Box 8)
  - Knight, C.A., Jr., 1941 (Box 8)
  - Knopf, Paul M., 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Koch, Arthur L., 1957 (Box 8)
  - Köhler, W., 1960 (Box 8)
  - Kondo, Mansaka, 1960 (Box 8)
  - König, H., 1950 (Box 8)
  - Koprowski, Hilary, 1957, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Kornberg, Arthur, 1972, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Kozinski, Andrzej W., 1951-1968, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Kozloff, Lloyd M., 1962-1965 (Box 8)
    -See also Ser.I, Journal of Virology
  - Kranzberg, Melvin (Box 8)
    -See Ser.I, Technology and Culture
  - Krimm, Sam, 1965-1967, n.d. (Box 8)
    -See also Ser.I, Moody, Michael F.
  - Kueppers, Friedrich, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Kushmerick, Martin, 1961 (Box 8)
  - Lafontaine, Jean G., 1954 (Box 8)
  - LaMer, Victor K., 1941 (Box 8)
    National Research Council. RCA Fellowship
  - Lancaster, Wayne D., 1985 (Box 8)
  - Lanni, Frank, 1953, 1961, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Lardy, Henry, 1941-1942 (Box 8)
  - Lark, Gordon, 1953 (Box 8)
  - Larsen, Joseph R., 1964 (Box 8)
    Stay, Barbara
  - Latarjet, Raymond, 1949-1978, n.d. (Box 8)
    -See also Ser.I, International Congress on Photobiology
  - Lauffer, Max A., 1942-1984 (Box 8)
    -See also Ser.I, Advances in Virus Research
  - Laven, H., 1953 (Box 8)
  - Lazarow, Arnold, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Lazo, Pedro A., 1985 (Box 8)
  - Le Poole, Jan B., 1960-1961, 1973 (Box 8)
    -See also Ser.I, International Federation of Societies for Electron Microscopy
  - Le Roy, Adrian, 1943 (Box 8)
  - Lederberg, Joshua, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Lee, Henry F., 1944 (Box 8)
  - Lehmann, E., 1961 (Box 8)
  - Lehr, Herndon B., 1957 (Box 8)
  - Lépine, P., 1953 (Box 8)
  - Levin, Bruce R., 1976 (Box 8)
  - Levine, Myron, 1960-1971 (Box 8)
    Israel, Vance
  - Levinthal, Cyrus, 1957-1958 (Box 8)
  - Levy, Stuart B., 1965 (Box 8)
  - Lewis, Aaron, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Lewis, Warren H., 1942 (Box 8)
  - The Library of Congress, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Lilly, 1951 (Box 8)
  - Lilly, John C., 1963 (Box 8)
  - Lindemann, B., 1950 (Box 8)
  - Little, K., 1962 (Box 8)
  - Litwin, Samuel, 1967 (Box 8)
  - Lloyd, J. Stanley, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Locquin, Marcel, 1953-1960 (Box 8)
  - Loeb, Lawrence, 1973 (Box 8)
    -See also Ser.I, Wells, Robert D.
  - Loeb, Marilyn R., 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Folder #1, 1968-1974 (Box 8)
    - Folder #2, 1975-1976, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Loewe, F., 1943 (Box 8)
  - London, W. Thomas, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Long Island Biological Association, 1953-1963 (Box 9)
  - Loring, Hubert S., 1942 (Box 9)
  - Low, Frank N., 1958 (Box 9)
  - Low, Kenneth Brooks, 1965, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Lowy, Douglas R., 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Luria, Salvador E., 1942-1978; 50.0 Item(s) (Box 9)
    Journal of Bacteriology
    -See also Ser.I, Delbrück, Max
    Bacterial genetics; Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Horwitz Prize; Fellowships, assistantships; Laboratory techniques, equipment; National Academy of Sciences; Publication; Teaching; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - LuValle, James E., 1953 (Box 9)
  - Lwoff, André, 1952-1978, n.d. (Box 9)
    -See also Ser.I, Bradbury, Phyllis Clarke
    -See also Ser.I, UNESCO
  - Maaløe, Ole, 1955-1961 (Box 9)
  - Maccacaro, G.A., 1961 (Box 9)
  - The MacMillan Company, 1949 (Box 9)
  - Maestre, Marcos F., 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - Magee, John L., 1942 (Box 9)
  - Malecki Laboratories, Inc., 1963 (Box 9)
  - Mallin, Morton Lewis, 1977 (Box 9)
  - Manigault, P., 1957 (Box 9)
  - Manning, Winston M., 1943 (Box 9)
  - Manowitz, Paul, 1963 (Box 9)
  - Manten, A., 1953 (Box 9)
  - Marine Biological Laboratory, 1942-1944 (Box 9)
    -See also Ser.II, Marine Biological Laboratory--Guest Register
  - Mark, George E., 1983-1986 (Box 9)
  - Markham, Roy, 1953 (Box 9)
  - Markhoff, Shirley, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Marshall, Bryan E., 1975 (Box 9)
  - Marton, L. (Bill), 1942 (Box 9)
  - Marwick, Charles, 1963 (Box 9)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1942 (Box 9)
    Schmitt, Francis O.
  - Massar, A.R., 1972 (Box 9)
  - Mathieu-Sicaud, Agnes, 1952 (Box 9)
  - Mathis, A., 1953 (Box 9)
  - Matsubara, Kenichi, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Matzke, Edwin B., 1958 (Box 9)
  - Mayhew, June N., 1967 (Box 9)
  - Mayor, Heather Donald, 1960-1961, 1968 (Box 9)
  - McClintock, Barbara, 1972, 1976 (Box 9)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc., 1958 (Box 9)
  - McMichael, Harrison, Jr., 1953 (Box 9)
  - McQuillen, Kenneth, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Meier, Russ, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Melechen, Norman E., 1953-1961 (Box 9)
  - Melnick, Joseph L., 1942 (Box 9)
  - Mennigman, Horst-Dieter, 1961-1962, 1972 (Box 9)
  - Mericle, Leo W., 1955 (Box 9)
  - Meryman, Harold T., 1953 (Box 9)
  - Meselson, Matthew, 1959, 1961 (Box 9)
  - Metz, C.W., 1941, 1959, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Metz, Jane, 1949 (Box 9)
  - Meyer, Harry M., Jr., 1973 (Box 9)
  - Mezger-Freed, Lisa, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Michel, Gertrude, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Mikulaszek, Edmund Juliusz, 1961-1962 (Box 9)
  - Mildvan, Albert S., n.d. (Box 9)
  - Miller, Gail L., 1962 (Box 9)
  - Miller, P.H., Jr., 1968 (Box 9)
  - Miller, Robert Carmi, Jr., 1969 (Box 9)
  - Millward, Stewart (Box 9)
    -See Ser.I, Graham, Angus F.
  - Mintz, Beatrice, 1969-1983 (Box 9)
  - Moe, Henry Allen, 1963 (Box 9)
  - Monod, Jacques, 1956, 1961, 1965 (Box 9)
  - Monsour, Victor, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Moody, Michael F., 1966 (Box 9)
    Krimm, Sam
  - Moore, Dan, 1965 (Box 9)
  - Moorjani, Sital, 1963-1964 (Box 9)
  - Morehead, Frederick F., 1958 (Box 9)
  - Morgan, Councilman, 1953-1971 (Box 9)
    Neter, Erwin
  - Morgand, P., 1967 (Box 9)
  - Morton, Harry E., 1941-1942, 1947, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Moses, Montrose J., 1958-1959 (Box 9)
  - Mota, Miguel, 1962, 1964 (Box 9)
  - Mudd, Emily, 1980 (Box 9)
  - Mudd, Stewart, 1959, 1967 (Box 9)
    -See also Ser.I, Nebel, Bernard R.
    -See also Ser.III, National Research Council. RCA Fellowship
  - Murray, Robert G.E., 1960, 1966-1967, n.d. (Box 9)
    -See also Ser.I, Bacteriological Reviews
  - Muscatine, Naomi (Box 9)
    -See Ser.I, Bloom, Naomi M.
  - Naegele, Robert Frank, 1965 (Box 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1964-1986 (Box 10)
  - National Health Education Committee, Inc., 1962-1964 (Box 10)
  - National Library of Medicine, 1957 (Box 10)
  - National Research Council (Canada), 1959 (Box 10)
  - National Science Foundation, 1960-1962 (Box 10)
    -See also Ser.III, same title
  - National Stereoscopic Association (Box 10)
    -See Ser.I, Fisher, Harold W.
  - Nature, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Nebel, Bernard R., 1941 (Box 10)
    Mudd, Stuart
  - Nelson, Oliver E., Jr. (Box 10)
    -See Ser.I, Owen, Ray D.
  - Neter, Erwin (Box 10)
    -See Ser.I, Morgan, Councilman
  - The New York Academy of Dentistry, 1941 (Box 10)
  - The New York Academy of Medicine, 1941-1949 (Box 10)
  - The New York Academy of Sciences, 1950-1968 (Box 10)
  - New York Microscopical Society, 1954-1955 (Box 10)
  - The New York Times, 1942 (Box 10)
  - Newcomer, H. Sidney, 1944 (Box 10)
  - Newell, Norman D., 1979 (Box 10)
  - Nichols, J.B., 1943 (Box 10)
  - Nicol, J.A. Colin, 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Niemann, Carl, 1958 (Box 10)
  - Niklowitz, W., 1961-1962 (Box 10)
  - Nimeck, M.W., 1962 (Box 10)
  - Nirenberg, Marshall, 1964-1965 (Box 10)
  - Noack, P., 1953 (Box 10)
  - Nonoyams, Meihan, 1972, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Nord, F.F., 1942 (Box 10)
  - Nowotny, Alois, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Nutting, George C., 1941 (Box 10)
  - Offner, Franklin F., 1964, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Ogston, Alexander G., 1979, 1981 (Box 10)
    -See also Ser.I, Blumberg, Baruch S.
  - Ogura, Yasuyuki, n.d. (Box 10)
  - Ohtsubo, Eiichi, 1978 (Box 10)
  - O'Kane, D.J., 1956 (Box 10)
  - Olson, John M., 1954-1958, n.d. (Box 10)
  - Oppenheimer, B.S., 1942 (Box 10)
  - Osborne, Daryll, 1939 (Box 10)
  - Oster, Carl F., Jr., 1953-1978, n.d. (Box 10)
  - Ou, Jonathan T., 1965, 1974, 1987-1988 (Box 10)
    -See also Ser.I, Rohm and Haas Company
  - Owen, Ray D., 1961-1984 (Box 10)
    Nelson, Oliver E., Jr.
  - Paglini, Severo, 1965 (Box 10)
  - Paik, Yong Kyun, 1965-1966 (Box 10)
  - Pakman, Leonard M., 1953-1962 (Box 10)
    Eisenberg, Roselyn
  - Palade, George E., 1963, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Pappenheimer, John R., 1965, 1979 (Box 10)
    -See also Ser.I, International Congress of Physiological Sciences
  - Park, Bo Han, 1956 (Box 10)
  - Parke, Davis and Company, 1943 (Box 10)
  - Parsons, Donald F., 1964, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1939-1981; 12.0 Item(s) (Box 10)
    American Association for the Advancement of Science; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Pauling, Linus. 75th birthday; Fellowships, assistantships -- Guggenheim; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Molecular genetics; Radiation genetics; Requests for aid in finding positions; Teaching
  - Pavan, Crodowaldo, n.d. (Box 10)
  - Pearson, H.E., 1956 (Box 10)
  - Pendergrass, Eugene P., 1956 (Box 10)
  - Pepe, Frank A., 1963-1967 (Box 10)
  - Perry, Robert P., 1961, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Perspectives in Biology and Medicine, 1971 (Box 10)
  - The Pennsylvania State University, 1940-1965 (Box 10)
  - Philadelphia Electron Microscope Society, 1954-1958, 1971 (Box 11)